翻译，压制: 布尔
字体: 思源黑体 Medium
思源黑体 Bold
You come on like a dream, peaches and cream
你就像个梦 桃子或者奶油
Lips like strawberry wine
嘴唇像是樱桃酒
You're sixteen, you're beautiful and you're mine
你16岁 很漂亮 是我的人了
So fine, baby you're mine
很好 你是我的人了
You're all ribbons and curls, you what a girl
你是打扮得如此漂亮的女孩
Eyes that twinkle and shine
眼睛闪闪发光
Now you're sixteen, you're beautiful and you're mine
现在你16岁 很漂亮 是我的人了
and you're mine
你是我的人了
Now you're my baby, you're my pet
现在你是我亲爱的 是我的宠物
We fell in love on the night we met
我们在见面的那晚上相爱
You touched my hand, my heart went pop
你摸着我的手 我心怦怦直跳
And Ooh, when we kissed we could not stop
我们亲吻时完全停不下来
You walked out of my dreams and into my arms
你从我梦中走出 进入我的怀抱
Now you're my angel divine
现在你就是我神圣的天使
Now you're sixteen, you're beautiful and you're mine
现在你16岁 很漂亮 是我的人了
and you're all mine
你我的人了
Now you're my baby, you're my pet
现在你是我亲爱的 是我的宠物
We fell in love on the night we met
我们在见面的那晚上相爱
You touched my hand, my little heart went pop...went pop
你摸着我的手 我那小心脏怦怦直跳
Oh my heart went pop
我心怦怦直跳
When we kissed we could not stop
我们亲吻时完全停不下来
You walked out of my dreams, and into my arms
你从我梦中走出 进入我的怀抱
Now you're my angel divine
现在你就是我神圣的天使
You're sixteen, you're beautiful, and you're mine
你16岁 很漂亮 是我的人了
Angel divine
神圣的天使
You're sixteen, you're beautiful, and you're mine
你16岁 很漂亮 是我的人了
注: 'Shoptimus Prime是该乐队乐队名
You come along baby, 'Shoptimus Prime
亲爱的 'Shoptimus Prime 你快过来
While you're my baby, beautiful
而你是我亲爱的 漂亮的
you're mine
你是我的人了
My angel divine
神圣的天使
mine so fine
我的人真是太好了
and you're mine
因为你是我的人了